<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Enterprise Architecture Aggregated News</title>
    <link>https://rss.tedt.org/aggregated_ea.xml</link>
    <description>Merged Enterprise Architecture sources</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>GitHub Action RSS Aggregator v2 (retention)</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 22:38:38 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Jekyll And Hyde: The Dual Role Of Disruptive Technologies In Sustainability (Source: www.forrester.com)</title>
      <link>https://www.forrester.com/blogs/jekyll-and-hyde-the-dual-role-of-disruptive-technologies-in-sustainability/</link>
      <description>Disruptive technologies such AI can boost efforts towards some strategic priorities, but can also work against environmental sustainability goals. Learn more about the the dual role played by six of the most important disruptive technologies poised to shape sustainability in 2025.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4d9653fc8d72a36728c1512555d7f81c</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2025 14:40:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IT Governance As A Secret Weapon: A Blueprint For Thriving In Chaos (Source: www.forrester.com)</title>
      <link>https://www.forrester.com/blogs/it-governance-as-a-secret-weapon-a-blueprint-for-thriving-in-chaos/</link>
      <description>Today’s technology executives face a perfect storm of market disruptions, shifting priorities, and relentless pressure to deliver. So why are most still operating with governance models built for a different era? Find out in this preview of our upcoming Technology &amp;#038; Innovation Summit North America.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">77e35a391e725075c7beaf335135b3ca</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 15:26:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>APAC Submissions Rock The Enterprise Architecture Awards — Are EMEA And North America Competitive? (Source: www.forrester.com)</title>
      <link>https://www.forrester.com/blogs/apac-submissions-rock-the-enterprise-architecture-awards-are-emea-and-north-america-competitive/</link>
      <description>The Asia-Pacific region’s submissions for our Enterprise Architecture Awards are very impressive. Can EA orgs in EMEA and the Americas rise to the same standard?</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e99f564295eb96aa25d61cc428b7ec36</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 14:01:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Forrester’s 2025 Enterprise Architecture Awards Winner And Runners-Up For APAC (Source: www.forrester.com)</title>
      <link>https://www.forrester.com/blogs/forresters-2025-enterprise-architecture-awards-winner-and-runners-up-for-apac/</link>
      <description>Congratulations to the Hong Kong Jockey Club, this year’s winner of the Enterprise Architecture Award in APAC, and runners-up AIA Group and Nan Shan Life Insurance Company. Learn how excellent EA practices helped all three align their IT strategies with business objectives, empowering them to accelerate business innovation and stay ahead of the curve.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">adb282b3f8b0dd6b6e5cc8028b8242e8</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2025 00:45:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mastering The Tightrope: How Strategic Portfolio Management Transforms Tech Leadership (Source: www.forrester.com)</title>
      <link>https://www.forrester.com/blogs/mastering-the-tightrope-how-strategic-portfolio-management-transforms-tech-leadership/</link>
      <description>CIOs routinely face a frustrating dilemma that drives them to ask the question: Am I truly spending the company’s money as effectively as possible? The answer lies in strategic portfolio management. Learn how this discipline is transforming how tech organizations approach their most critical decisions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a531f2b912a40de0f0fe7c696649ed3d</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 18:37:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Navigate With Confidence The Migration Options For SAP ECC Customers (Source: www.forrester.com)</title>
      <link>https://www.forrester.com/blogs/navigate-with-confidence-the-migration-options-for-sap-ecc-customers/</link>
      <description>The clock is ticking on SAP ECC’s end-of-support date in 2027, and the big question requiring your attention is: What’s your plan to get to SAP S/4HANA cloud? Learn the options in this preview of an upcoming peer discussion for Forrester clients.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c78c33e6a1ce7dc165b2f9b1a64c99a5</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 17:30:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Google Cloud Unveils New Data Security Posture Management Offering in Preview (Source: feed.infoq.com)</title>
      <link>https://www.infoq.com/news/2025/08/google-cloud-dspm-preview/?utm_campaign=infoq_content&amp;utm_source=infoq&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_term=Enterprise+Architecture</link>
      <description>&lt;img src="https://www.infoq.com/styles/static/images/logo/logo_bigger.jpg"/&gt;&lt;p&gt;Google Cloud unveils its new Data Security Posture Management (DSPM) offering, enhancing data governance, privacy, and compliance. This innovative solution provides visibility into sensitive data, helping organizations identify risks and enforce controls. With advanced features integrated into the Security Command Center, it addresses the evolving challenges of cloud data security.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;i&gt;By Steef-Jan Wiggers&lt;/i&gt;</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f1b889297bcf9f0d9b690d132a5f4253</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Agentic AI Elevates The Enterprise Architect’s Role (Source: www.forrester.com)</title>
      <link>https://www.forrester.com/blogs/the-future-of-the-enterprise-architects-job/</link>
      <description>As agentic AI becomes embedded in enterprise architecture tools, it’s not just automating tasks — it’s redefining the architect’s role. Learn five things enterprise architects can do to adapt to their new reality.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f90773f3efdc3911036847f9342e9289</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 03:59:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jira integration enhanced: connecting EA planning to IT execution (Source: www.leanix.net)</title>
      <link>https://www.leanix.net/en/blog/jira-integration-enhanced</link>
      <description>&lt;div class="hs-featured-image-wrapper"&gt; 
 &lt;a href="https://www.leanix.net/en/blog/jira-integration-enhanced" title="" class="hs-featured-image-link"&gt; &lt;img src="https://www.leanix.net/hubfs/Jira%20integration%20enhanced%20connecting%20EA%20planning%20to%20IT%20execution.jpg" alt="Jira integration enhanced: connecting EA planning to IT execution" class="hs-featured-image" style="width:auto !important; max-width:50%; float:left; margin:0 15px 15px 0;"&gt; &lt;/a&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt; 
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;SAP LeanIX Jira integration has been a key feature of our solution for a long time, but this capability will soon become even more essential. Discover our upcoming enhanced Jira integration and how it will level up your enterprise architecture execution.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a4f39dccc10cccbf3fd9a36fac108f19</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Sep 2025 13:27:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
